Figma is gone and you are missing it and
we know that because we are missing it
too and it was already like just today.
We built a road map in a week that we
were dreaming of for months because
Figma was so great, but now it's gone.
So, what are the alternatives? We are
going to dig into that in this video.
So, subscribe, watch the video, and
like, and share it with your friends.
Woo! Woo! So, what did you do with Figma
5?
>> Everything.
>> Yeah.
>> I just I I don't check every project and
then create a lot of documentation and
then I was at 2% so I thought, well,
let's go.
>> At some point the models will also be
able to write better code that any found
engineers.
>> Yeah. So, they don't you don't write it.
You just test it if it is user-friendly.
>> Yes, what I do is like I run the app on
local and even on production like with
the extension and then Claude is click
click on the app and then I can say,
"Okay, this one is broken." And then
change that, then you still have to
describe what you want, but it's getting
better and better and yes, soon enough
it should like memorize what you want or
even like have the guidelines of all of
the project and keep following the
guidelines and the MD file that you
have. So, then it's done. Like it knows
that I don't want it to not use my
shared component like a card or a table.
I don't want him to create a HTML table.
I I want it to use my table component so
then it will always looks the same.
>> Right?
>> Yeah. That's perfect.
>> It's just like you have a wide engineers
that need quadrilles and your job is
just like giving like putting on the
rails, but yeah, it can execute crazy
stuff. For example, I never coded with
Swift. I always did like hybrid apps,
but now I have two or three apps that I
use on my Mac like Mac Swift clean and
the metal bar stuff. Completely Swift
Swift native code. Never read a line of
code. Okay, it's a small tool stuff,
right? But it works. I have a nice user
experience with it, and that's it.
>> And that's perfect. And you use it for
yourself, so it's not to scale and
>> Yes. And yeah, and it doesn't need to
scale like crazy in in term of, okay,
it's going to touch your computer. It's
open source, so people can review the
code, whatever, whatever. So it's fine.
Yes, okay, I'm not building Twitch, so
fair enough.
>> I think that's still also a big
difference. Some of the tools that I
make that are running locally or even in
the GitHub and we just pull them to
everybody in the company, but everybody
runs it locally, not on the internet,
then yeah, just let it run. I don't even
check it. It just needs to work.
>> On on this Arena benchmark stuff, 5.5.2
max is at the level of 5.4i,
which is also massive. But they have the
distillation basically, so frontier
model launch model, private get this
still, zed.ai or any other like deep
seek is distilling those models, get the
the open source model back, sell
subscription, boom.
>> Yes, true.
>> Like we legit have one generation away,
so basically three to six months lag
between frontier and open source models.
So that means in like 12 to 18 months,
we will have open source model who have
stable five intelligence.
>> Yeah, that's insane. But by that time, I
hope to have built so much it doesn't
>> But what are you going to build?
>> Everything. No, but before you had to
plan because building a proper software
tool would take you at least a year to
do it properly, sales and everything.
And now you just choose a niche, you
build it within two, three days, and you
start selling.
>> Yeah. Yeah, I try that.
>> Yeah, you're making like a huge system
with every functionality.
>> Yeah. I I I I think, okay, so you know,
I think you're right. Like with those
model now, we can even see big wave of
one shot software.
>> Yeah.
>> Because yeah, I I even like the the game
like so the the game we won one shot
prompted. Okay, that's that's a little
bit buggy, but you spend like one or two
days on it. Then you have proper
something like proper like something
with what which is fun. And then you can
market these games to We're going to
have a lot of stream Steam games slope,
especially when Unreal Engine is making
it like MCP and then everyone can
access. Yeah.
>> Yeah, yeah. Talk to it and it will build
it.
>> Yeah, exactly. But we're getting
>> Yeah, like for sure. And yeah, like for
those Fable 5 level models. Yeah, bro,
we we have 12 months to cook like
starting now.
>> What are we going to build?
>> So, based on Fable feedback, I asked
GPT-5 to where should we take this road
map direction, blah blah blah. And I
could build a SaaS for generating
assets. Like kind of like Genfeed, but
with like the vertical of gaming where
you have your own studio inside of the
Yeah, and that's it. But yeah, I would
And then open source and whatever. There
is a couple of open source solution, but
probably can do something better. I
don't know. So, there is that still
Genfeed and still like customers project
that where we can either do mega apps of
one verticals that do everything or
small small tiny SaaS micro SaaSes, but
then you make like 10 20 of them and
hopefully some of them catch up to 5 10k
20k a month.
>> I know. Well, that's good enough. And if
you have like five to 10 of those,
that's perfect.
>> Exactly. There is a lot of like indie
hackers the who are basically doing
that, but you can serve them like the
the the the world is your oyster, right?
So, you can keep building some stuff
that works. And yeah, just try it out.
And if it doesn't work, you trash it.
You go to the next one.
>> Yeah, you just improve it or delete it.
>> I show you this this software, right?
So, it's it's a platform where you
connect your Stripe key in read-only and
you can see the revenue of those
platform. So, so then those platform can
like the founder can flex, "Oh, yeah, I
build a I have coded this app, and then
this is my revenue. Trust me because I'm
on Trust Mirror."
>> Yeah.
>> And but what's smart too is now that you
can buy SaaS that are generating
revenue. Like, if you want to buy Eric's
AI visibility SaaS with a paid growth
dashboard for businesses that I want to
be automated by ChatGPT clone. Okay, so
it's a geo business making revenue, blah
blah blah, boom, and you can see the
whole revenue based on Stripe stuff, and
contact the guy and try to buy the
>> Yeah, buy the SaaS, and so you have some
they prove that it is making money.
>> Exactly. But what's tricky if if I see
that, "How hard can I replicate the
product in a week and start sales week
two?"
>> Yeah, but eventually it's not about
building, it's about doing proper sales.
>> Exactly. But if you are if you are an
influencer with like some distribution
channels, then
I putting that that's awesome. Yeah. So,
yeah, and okay, so this guy from back
from this platform where yeah, Mark Lou,
perfect. Bath. So, he has all of his
business on his own landing page. Code
fast, 9K. Ship fast, 3K a month. Data
fast, 20K. Trust Mirror, 37K a month for
the platform. Focus on your startup
knowing the invoice, 100 a month. Proper
Okay, so he gets some SaaS that's going
nowhere. But okay.
>> build a lot and only focus on the few
that take off.
>> Yeah, but like Trust Mirror, in 1 month
you pay for all of your Looks like meme
coin, bro.
>> Yeah.
>> Like, you buy one meme coin, you you win
one, and then you you pay back for 1,000
1,000 fail and scam that you have
invested. But yeah, okay. So, look, he's
making like a 100K ones.
>> I think his biggest product is this
website because he is getting so many
DMs from pretty women who want someone
who has money.
>> Exactly. The indie page.
>> Okay.
>> Indie page, nice. Okay, that's pretty
cool. Yeah, see like those kind of like
that's that's perfect. One pass 25
years, lifetime deal. Yeah, so basically
it's a link link tree page, but for all
of the indie hacker, boom. And he has
like YouTube channel with like 200,000
subscribers. So,
>> Yeah.
>> Distribution. As soon as you have
distribution, you can do all of those
small projects.
>> And it doesn't even matter what you
build.
>> Exactly. Exactly. So, yeah. That's the
alternative to 5.5.
>> Great content.
>> Yeah. I like I like this mindset of like
and AI is perfect for that. I like it.
So cool. I'm like right now I'm kind of
like waiting for 5.6 to drop now. Like
>> Yeah. So, we are just refreshing the
timeline all the time waiting for the
moment that they pushed
>> Yeah. Because okay, so if you use 5.5
now, like how much slope are you going
to push?
>> But it doesn't matter. You can either
prompt write prompts or you can now just
build with 5.5, put it in different
branch, and as soon as the 5.6 comes
out, you say, "Hey, this was my branch.
Check everything." And it will optimize
your code.
>> So, you push as much PR that you can,
and then you will review everything.
Yeah, makes sense.
>> Yeah. And you don't have to explain what
you want to do.
>> Yeah. So, basically you prepare for the
next upcoming models. Hopefully we're
not going to have to wait to
to many things, and that's going to
>> Yeah, I have like over 100 branches with
code waiting to be reviewed.
>> But you you know that's what feel like
something again like feel another video
of his like
he was on the conversation conference,
and he was recording on his on his
history card mobile app, and Fabel
shipped what he thought would take a
months to review and ship, and he didn't
have to review as much as it was
reviewing before.
>> Yeah, but before we were building with
5.5 as well, so
>> Yeah, I know. Exactly.
>> it won't be that big of an issue.
>> But you you don't know Okay, I don't
know what I ship until it's broken.
>> We will give an update on the channel
once 5.6 is out.
>> Yes, I think we have we have our stream
for next week. That's for sure. Okay,
the alternative doesn't exist. Bye. End
of the video. Let's go. Mitchell, thank
you so much for your time and uh
Let's get back to prompting some plans
that we will review by smarter models.
>> [laughter]
>> Awesome. Thank you. Enjoy your day.